FreeBSD's Privacy Policy
========================

Privacy Policy
--------------

The FreeBSD Project recognizes that your privacy and the protection of your personal information is important to you and is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the measures taken by us to protect your privacy in connection with your use of www.FreeBSD.org and docs.FreeBSD.org (our "Sites"). This policy does not cover mirrors of this content on other hosts (the "Mirrors") or other FreeBSD-related services in the FreeBSD.org domain ("Affiliated Sites").

This policy was last modified on October 14, 2022.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY USING THIS SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS POLICY.

What information is collected on our Sites:
-------------------------------------------

We collect weblogs such as your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type and operating system information. No personal data is kept in logs for more than 30 days. The foregoing information is collectively referred to below as "Your Usage Data."

We store information such as your email address, name, and organization or company ("Personally Identifiable Information") only if you decide to send us such information by submitting a FreeBSD bug or problem report ("PR"), subscribing to one of the FreeBSD mailing lists, posting content to our Site forums or sending a review to Phabricator. The FreeBSD Project allows unlimited distribution of that content. Information submitted in those reports and lists, including your Personally Identifiable Information, is considered public and will be accessible to anyone on the web. Such information is not only stored on servers belonging to the FreeBSD Foundation, but it is also stored on other servers that mirror the content of our Sites. The FreeBSD Foundation has no control over the use of that information, including your Personally Identifiable Information.

Use of Cookies
--------------

Only our [Bug tracking system](https://bugs.freebsd.org/), [Forums](https://forums.freebsd.org/), [Wiki](https://wiki.freebsd.org/) and [Reviews](https://reviews.freebsd.org/) pages will store [Cookies](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) in your computer to personalize content, tailor your experience, and allow you to login to these pages. A cookie is a small text file provided by a web server that may be placed on your computer by your web browser. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this or other websites.

How the information collected is used:
--------------------------------------

The FreeBSD Project takes the privacy of our users and members very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties except as stated in this document. We will not associate any data gathered from your use of our Sites with any personally identifying information.

The FreeBSD Project will not use or share your personal information in a manner that differs from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your prior consent.

How your information is protected:
----------------------------------

The FreeBSD Project strictly protects the security of the personal information you provide. Personal information we collect is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access, and we carefully protect this information from loss or misuse, and from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

When your information may be disclosed:
---------------------------------------

The FreeBSD Project may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

1. conform to the requirements of the law or comply with legal process served on The FreeBSD Project or the Sites;
    
2. protect and defend the rights or property of The FreeBSD Project; or
    
3. act in urgent circumstances to protect personal safety of users of The FreeBSD Project, its websites, or the public.

Anonymized aggregate traffic data about website visits may be shared for marketing or research purposes.

The FreeBSD Project does not share un-anonymised data with anyone.

Updates to this privacy policy:
-------------------------------

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last modified" date at the top of the Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

Sale of assets:
---------------

In the unlikely event that The FreeBSD Project or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your information may be one of the transferred assets.

Third party links:
------------------

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our sites. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only covers our Sites and does not cover any other website. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our sites and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

Contacting Us:
--------------

We would like to receive your comments and questions about this Privacy Policy and any other matter you have regarding our Sites. Please address comments or questions to us via e-mail at: [privacy@FreeBSD.org](mailto:privacy@FreeBSD.org).

* * *

**Last modified on**: October 14, 2022 by [Sergio Carlavilla Delgado](https://cgit.freebsd.org/doc/commit/?id=5816b53ddd)

[Legal Notices](https://www.freebsd.org/copyright/) | © 1995-2024 The FreeBSD Project All rights reserved. The mark FreeBSD is a registered trademark of The FreeBSD Foundation and is used by The FreeBSD Project with the permission of [The FreeBSD Foundation](https://www.freebsdfoundation.org/legal/trademark-usage-terms-and-conditions/). [Contact](https://www.freebsd.org/mailto/)
